
   {
       "questions":[
           {"question":"A module created by using the AngularJS function is called?","answers":["module","module()","mod()","angular module()"],"correct":2},
           {"question":"How many $RootScope an AngularJS application can have?","answers":["Zero","One","Two","Infinity"],"correct":2},
           {"question":"AngularJS is perfect for?","answers":["MPAs","DPAs","SPAs","CPAs"],"correct":3},
           {"question":"Which of the following is the correct syntax for writing AngularJS expressions?","answers":["{{expression}}","(expression)","{{{expression}}}","[expression]"],"correct":1},
           {"question":"What is deep linking in AngularJS?","answers":["Deep linking is an SEO-based technique.","Deep linking refers to linking various views to the main page.","Deep linking allows you to encode the state of an application in the URL so that it can be bookmarked.","All of the Above"],"correct":3},
           {"question":"Which of the following is an advantage of AngularJS?","answers":["AngularJS code is unit testable.","AngularJS provides reusable components.","AngularJS uses dependency injection and makes use of separation of concerns.","All of the above"],"correct":4},
           {"question":"AngularJS applications are a mix of which of the following technologies?","answers":["HTML and PHP","HTML and JavaScript","HTML and TypeScript","PHP and JavaScript"],"correct":2},
           {"question":"Which of the following is used to share data between controller and view in AngularJS?","answers":["using Model","using services","using factory","using $scope"],"correct":2},
           {"question":"The [] parameter in the module definition is used to define dependent modules.","answers":["TRUE","FALSE","Can be true or false","Cannot say"],"correct":1},
           {"question":" In AngularJS, the $http service is used to make an Ajax call to the server.","answers":["True","False"],"correct":1}
        ]
   }   